Guide to the Sara and Gerald Murphy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1880-1990s; Series III; 12.84 linear feet (43 boxes)
  - Snapshots and Candid Portraits
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1925-1926 (Box 28, Folder 558)
      Includes photographs of Sir Charles Mendl, Elsie de Wolfe, Monty Woolley, Ada MacLeish, Ada and Archibald MacLeish's children, F. Scott Fitzgerald, and Zelda Fitzgerald
    - Photographs of children's art show (salon de la jeunesse), circa 1926 (Box 29, Folder 559)
    - Murphy family and guests dining in a garden, 1926 (Box 29, Folder 560)
      Possibly New Year's Day
    - Sara and Gerald Murphy with Ada and Archibald MacLeish, Vienna, Austria, 1927 February (Box 29, Folder 561)
    - Sara with Honoria, Baoth, and Patrick, and Henriette Géron, Madeira, Portugal, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 562)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1927 (Box 29, Folder 563)
      Includes photographs of Harpo Marx
    - Donald Ogden Stewart, Bea Stewart, and Ames Stewart, circa 1927 (Box 29, Folder 564)
    - Gerald Murphy, Vladimir Orloff, and ship builders posing beside the newly built sailboat Honoria, 1928 Spring (Box 29, Folder 565)
    - Gerald Murphy, Vladimir Orloff, and crew sailing Honoria, circa 1928 (Box 29, Folder 566)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 567-568)
      Includes photographs of Marisse Hamilton, Peter Hamilton, and Monty Woolley
    - Murphy children with Henriette Géron, Baden Baden, Germany, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 569)
    - Murphy family, Beverly Hills, California, 1928-1929 (Box 29, Folder 570)
    - Murphy family on ocean liner returning to France, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 571)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1929 Summer (Box 29, Folder 572)
      Includes photographs of Dorothy Parker, Ellen Barry, Philip Barry, Robert Benchley, Zelda Fitzgerald
    - Murphy family, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, 1929 October - 1931 (Box 29, Folder 573-578)
      Includes photographs of Monty Woolley, Dorothy Parker, Archibald MacLeish, Ada MacLeish, and tutor Yvonne Roussell. Other photographs include snapshots of the Murphy's home La Bruyère
    - Harrys Bar, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, 1929-1931 (Box 29, Folder 579)
      Photograph postcards and snapshots of bar "Harrys" owned and operated by the Murphys
    - Honoria with tutor M.B. Descheneaux, Montana-Vermala, Switzerland, 1929-1930 (Box 29, Folder 580)
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria, and Baoth, Venice, Italy, 1931 Spring (Box 30, Folder 581)
    - Murphy family, Ramgut, Bad Aussee, Austria, 1931 July-August (Box 30, Folder 582)
      Includes photographs of Fernand Léger, Scottie Fitzgerald, and Pickman family
    - Sara, Honoria, and Pickmans, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 583)
      Possibly in Austria
    - Baoth Murphy's school, Neubeuern, Rosenheim, Germany, 1930-1931 (Box 30, Folder 584)
    - Archibald MacLeish and his children, Conway, Massachusetts, circa 1929 (Box 30, Folder 585)
    - Sara and Gerald Murphy, Vladimir Orloff with sailboat Weatherbird, 1931 (Box 30, Folder 586)
      Includes one photograph with Philip Barry
    - Gerald and Honoria Murphy with MacLeishes, Conway, Massachusetts, 1931 September (Box 30, Folder 587)
    - Murphy family at home in Bedford Village, New York, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 588-589)
    - Murphy family, Antibes, France, 1932 Spring (Box 30, Folder 590)
    - Murphys onboard the Weatherbird with Philip Barry and Ellen Barry, 1932 (Box 30, Folder 591)
    - Patrick in Canada, 1932 May (Box 30, Folder 592)
    - Murphy family with Ernest Hemingway and Pauline Pfeiffer, L Bar T Ranch, Montana, 1932 August (Box 30, Folder 593)
    - Honoria at Convent of the Sacred Heart, Noroton, Connecticut, 1932 Fall (Box 30, Folder 594)
    - Patrick rabbit hunting, East Hampton, Long Island, New York, circa 1932 (Box 30, Folder 595)
    - Gerald, Baoth, and Patrick hunting with Archibald MacLeish, circa 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 596)
    - Archibald MacLeish visiting East Hampton, Long Island, New York, circa 1932-1933 (Box 30, Folder 597)
    - Gerald with Honoria, Baoth, and Patrick on beach, East Hampton, Long Island, New York, circa 1933 (Box 30, Folder 598)
    - Honoria with Louise Dowdney, Rosemary Hall, Greenwich, Connecticut, circa 1933-1935 (Box 30, Folder 599)
    - Sara with Ellen Barry and Pauline Pfeiffer, Florida, 1934 April (Box 31, Folder 600)
    - Murphy family at Palo Corona Ranch owned by Olga Wiborg Fish and Sidney Fish, Carmel, California, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 601)
    - Murphy family sailing on Weatherbird from Antibes to Marseilles, France, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 602)
      Includes photographs of Vladimir Orloff, Fanny Myers, and Villa America
    - Murphy family sailing on the Weatherbird in the Mediterranean, 1934 (Box 31, Folder 603-607)
      Includes photographs of Vladimir Orloff, Fanny Myers, John Dos Passos, Katy Dos Passos, Richard Cowan, and Villa America
    - Photographs of the Weatherbird, 1930s (Box 31, Folder 608-609)
    - Honoria in Antibes, France, circa 1934 (Box 31, Folder 610)
    - Olga Wiborg Fish, Sidney Fish, and Stuyvesant Fish, East Hampton, Long Island, 1934 August (Box 31, Folder 611)
    - Murphy family, Saranac Lake, New York, 1935-1936 (Box 31, Folder 612-613)
      Includes photographs of Alice Lee Myers, Archibald MacLeish, Ada MacLeish, Richard Cowan, and Sidney Fish; Murphys' homes Steele Camp and Camp Adeline; and Dr. Gary Trudeau with family at Lake Placid during the winter Olympics
    - Murphy family, Saranac Lake, New York, 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 614-615)
    - Sara Murphy, Fernand Léger, Archibald MacLeish, Ada MacLeish, Marie Bissell, Dick Myers, and others before and during the Paper Ball, Hartford, Connecticut, 1936 February (Box 32, Folder 616)
    - Olga Wiborg Fish with unidentified people, Palo Corona Ranch, Carmel, California, 1935-1936 (Box 32, Folder 617)
    - Olga Wiborg Fish, Sidney Fish, and Stuyvesant Fish, Palo Corona Ranch, Carmel, California, before 1937 (Box 32, Folder 618-619)
    - Sara Murphy visiting Fish family following Olga's death, Palo Corona Ranch, Carmel, California, 1937 Spring (Box 32, Folder 620)
    - Honoria holding dog, 1937 (Box 32, Folder 621)
    - Honoria on vacation with Alice Lee Myers, Fanny Myers, and Frances "Scottie" Fitzgerald (?), Europe, 1937 Summer (Box 32, Folder 622)
    - Sara, Gerald, and Honoria with Louise Dowdney sailing on the Weatherbird, 1938 Summer (Box 32, Folder 623)
    - Noël Haskins Murphy serving with Comité Américain de Secours Civil, France, circa 1938 (Box 32, Folder 624)
    - Gerald Murphy wearing fake beard with Alexander Woolcott, Neshobe, Lake Bomoseen, Vermont, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 625)
    - Murphys hosting dinner party and garden party with Murphy children, Dorothy Parker, Philip Barry, Robert Benchley, Marc Connelly, Donald Stewart and other unidentified guests, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 626)
    - Gerald Murphy playing croquet with Harpo Marx and others, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 627)
    - Sara and Gerald in desert and Sara at home Hook Pond, East Hampton, Long Island, New York, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 628)
    - Sara and Gerald, East Hampton and Bedford Village, New York, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 629)
    - Sara with Philip Barry, Ellen Barry and their sons, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 630)
    - Patrick Murphy and Anna Murphy, South Hampton, Long Island, New York, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 631)
    - Frank Wiborg, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 632)
    - Honoria with young girl standing in front of unidentified home, Honoria on terrace, Honoria wearing fingerless gloves with head resting on back of chair, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 633)
    - Baoth dressed in women's pioneer clothing, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 634)
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria and friends at Hook Pond, East Hampton, New York, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 635)
      Includes photographs of Fernand Léger, Alice Lee Myers, and Virginia Pfeiffer
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria and friends at Hook Pond, East Hampton, New York, negatives, 1930s (Box 207, Folder 1651)
    - Archibald MacLeish, Key West, Florida, 1930s (Box 32, Folder 636)
    - Baoth with classmates, by Thompson, Yonkers, New York, 1930s
    - Various photographs of Lillie Nyberg, 1930s-1940s (Box 32, Folder 637)
    - Philip Barry at his home in Easthampton, New York, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 638)
    - Wedding of Honoria and John Shelton, East Hampton, New York, and Honoria and Shelton in Scotland, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 639)
    - Vladimir Orloff, Fanny Myers, Kate Duffy, Paul (?), and Joseph Revello, Villa America, Antibes, France, 1945 (Box 32, Folder 640)
    - Sara Murphy with Honoria and grandchildren, Nassau, Bahamas, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 641)
    - Sara Murphy with Honoria and grandchildren, Nassau, Bahamas, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 642)
    - Sara Murphy with Ada MacLeish and Archibald MacLeish, Nassau, Bahamas, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 643)
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria, Rusty St. John, and unidentified men, Sneden's Landing, New York, 1949 (Box 33, Folder 644)
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria, Lloyd Lowndes, Marion Lowndes, and Susan Lowndes, Sneden's Landing, New York, circa 1949 (Box 33, Folder 645)
    - Honoria on lawn at Sneden's Landing, New York, circa 1949 (Box 33, Folder 646)
    - Sara, Gerald, Honoria, Hank, and unidentified people, Sneden's Landing, New York, circa 1949 (Box 33, Folder 647)
    - Various photographs of Honoria, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 648)
      Includes photograph of Honoria with Norris Houghton and holding small child
    - Sara Murphy with John Dos Passos, Katy Dos Passos, Lloyd Lowndes, Diddy Lowndes, and others at Cheer Hall, Sneden's Landing, New York, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 649)
    - Gerald Murphy at meeting of the Hat Club, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 650)
    - Gerald Murphy (wearing leather jacket with fur collar) and friends, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 651)
    - Gerald at formal dinner, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 652)
    - Gerald wearing shorts and sandals, possibly at Sneden's Landing, New York, 1940s (Box 33, Folder 653)
    - Wedding of Honoria and John Donnelly and christening of John Charles Baoth Donnelly, 1950, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 654)
    - Sara visiting Honoria and John Donnelly, Carmel and San Francisco, California, circa 1951 (Box 33, Folder 655)
    - Sara at christening of Lucy Dos Passos, Spence's Point, Virginia, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 656)
    - Sara and Gerald with Dos Passos family, 1954-1959 (Box 33, Folder 657)
    - Sara and Gerald, East Hampton, New York, 1954-1959 (Box 33, Folder 658)
    - Sara and Gerald, East Hampton, New York, 1960 Summer (Box 207, Folder 1652)
    - Various photographs of Noël Haskins Murphy with friends and in garden, 1956-1970, undated (Box 33, Folder 659)
    - John Dos Passos, Betty Dos Passos, Lucy Dos Passos, Christopher "Kiffy" Holdridge, and others, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 660)
      Includes photographs of Lucy Dos Passos's first birthday, Dos Passos home at Spence's Point, and Dos Passos family traveling
    - Sara sleeping with dog on her chest, possibly at East Hampton, Long Island, New York, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 661)
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 662)
      Includes negatives without prints
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, 1950s (Box 34, Folder 663-672)
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, 1950s (Box 35, Folder 673-686)
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, 1950s (Box 36, Folder 687)
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, negatives, 1950s (Box 207, Folder 1653-1663)
    - Sara and Gerald with Honoria, John Donnelly, and grandchildren, Carmel, California, and East Hampton, New York, negatives, 1960s (Box 208, Folder 1664-1672)
    - Sara and Gerald with family and friends, East Hampton and Sneden's Landing, New York, 1960-1966 (Box 36, Folder 688)
      Includes photograph of Gerald clearing the beach
    - Sara and Gerald with family and friends, East Hampton and Sneden's Landing, New York, negatives, 1960-1966 (Box 208, Folder 1673)
    - Sara and Gerald at home photographed by tenant, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 689)
      Includes photograph of Gerald sitting in front of Fernand Léger painting
    - Sara and Gerald, Sneden's Landing, New York, before 1963 (Box 36, Folder 690)
    - Sara and Gerald with John Dos Passos and Lucy Dos Passos, Sneden's Landing, New York and John Dos Passos with Lucy Dos Passos, 1963, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 691)
    - Sara, Honoria, and grandchildren, East Hampton, New York, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 692)
    - Honoria, John Donnelly, and children, 1960s (Box 36, Folder 693-700)
    - Honoria, Betty Dos Passos, and Lucy Dos Passos at exhibition on John Dos Passos, F. Scott Fitzgerald, and Ernest Hemingway, University of Virginia, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 701)
    - Donnelly children, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 702)
    - Honoria at signing for her book Sara and Gerald, Georgetown, Washington, D.C., 1983 (Box 37, Folder 703)
    - Wedding of Laura Donnelly and Adrian Clemens Taylor, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 704)
      See also: Wiborg family by E.B. Core, Cincinnati, Ohio
    - Honoria and John Donnelly with grandson and 38th wedding anniversary, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 705)
    - Honoria and John Donnelly, Normandy, France and East Hampton, New York, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 706)
      Includes slides
    - Honoria and Laura Donnelly, Normandy, France, 1989 June (Box 37, Folder 707)
    - Honoria with children and grandchildren, East Hampton, New York, 1992-1994 (Box 37, Folder 708-709)
    - Honoria with children at opening of exhibition "Americans in Paris" with artwork by Gerald Murphy, Phillips Collection, Washington, D.C., 1996 (Box 37, Folder 710)
    - Honoria's 80th birthday party, New York, New York, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 711)
    - Various photographs of Honoria and John Donnelly with family and friends, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 712)
    - Gerald standing on a rock with a towel wrapped around his head, undated (Box 37, Folder 713)
    - Gerald in Chinese robe given to him by Archibald MacLeish, undated (Box 37, Folder 714)
    - Honoria sailing, negatives, undated (Box 209, Folder 1674)
    - Honoria on train trip and baby, negatives, undated (Box 209, Folder 1675)
    - Bob Benchley as young man, undated (Box 37, Folder 715)
    - Bob Benchley and Donald Ogden Stewart play fighting, undated (Box 37, Folder 716)
    - S.J. Perlman, Gilbert Seldes (?), Lester Donohue, and Noel Coward, undated (Box 37, Folder 717)
    - Various photographs of friends' children including Amos Stewart, Susan Lowndes, Benet children and others, undated (Box 37, Folder 718)
    - Four unidentified men standing outside of business with sign "A. Wiborg", undated (Box 37, Folder 719)
    - Eric Portman performing in outdoor theater, London, England, undated (Box 37, Folder 720)
    - La Désirade, Antilles, undated (Box 37, Folder 721)
    - Various locations including Parknasilla, Ireland; Java; Fontainebleau (France) and unidentified locations, undated (Box 38, Folder 722)
    - Various locations including Parknasilla, Ireland; Java; Fontainebleau (France) and unidentified locations, negatives, undated (Box 209, Folder 1676)
    - Unidentified cruise ship, negatives, undated (Box 209, Folder 1677)
    - Photograph composite of lucite Mark Cross emblem, Patrick Murphy, and of drawing of Mark Cross store front, undated (Box 38, Folder 723)
    - Various photographs of the Murphys' pets, undated (Box 38, Folder 724)
    - Copies of photographs of Baoth and Patrick, largely sailing on Weatherbird, undated (Box 38, Folder 725)
    - Copies of photographs largely of Antibes and sailing on Weatherbird, undated (Box 38, Folder 726)
    - Copies of negatives largely of Murphys with Hemingway, undated (Box 38, Folder 727)
    - Copies of photographs mounted on board, undated (Box 38, Folder 728-735)
    - Copies of photographs mounted on board, undated (Box 39, Folder 736)
    - Empty negative folders, undated (Box 39, Folder 737)
    - Family Homes
      - Wiborg mansion, Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio
        - Exterior view with people playing croquet on lawn, circa 1880
      - The Dunes, East Hampton, Long Island, New York
        - Photographs of the exterior and interior, after 1896 (Box 39, Folder 738-739)
        - Photographs of the Italian garden, after 1896 (Box 39, Folder 740)
          Includes photographs by Frances Benjamin Johnston and Mattie Edwards Hewitt, New York
        - Postcard photographs, after 1896 (Box 39, Folder 741)
          Includes lithograph postcards by Americhrome and H.O. Korten
        - Aerial photographs, circa 1940, 1984, undated (Box 39, Folder 742)
          Includes real estate advertisement by Pease and Elliman featuring aerial photograph as well as photographs by Fairchild Aerial Surveys and Eagle Eye Aerial Photography
      - Cambridge, Massachusetts
        - Murphys' homes in Cambridge during 1920s, undated (Box 39, Folder 743)
      - Villa America, Antibes, France
        - Photographs of exterior, 1920s (Box 39, Folder 744-745)
          Includes photographs from before renovation
        - Photograph postcards, 1920s (Box 39, Folder 746)
        - Panoramic photographs of view from Villa America, 1920s (Box 39, Folder 747)
        - Photographs of exterior with Joseph and Baptistine Revello, 1940s (Box 39, Folder 748-749)
        - Photographs of Villa America when owned by Edmund Uher, before 1976, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 750)
        - Photographs of Villa America when owned by Edmund Uher, before 1976, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 751)
        - Photographs of Honoria, John Donnelly, and sons at Villa America, 1978-1980 (Box 40, Folder 752-754)
          Includes photographs with Joseph and Baptistine Revello
        - Photographs of Villa America undergoing renovations, sent by François Fretiere, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 755)
        - Copies of photographs of Villa America, undated (Box 40, Folder 756)
      - Hook Pond and Swan Cove, East Hampton, Long Island, New York
        - Hook Pond, 1947 (Box 40, Folder 757)
        - Swan Cove, 1940s (Box 40, Folder 758)
        - Various photographs and postcards of East Hampton, 1940s-1990s (Box 40, Folder 759)
          Includes photographs of La Petite Hutte
      - Cheer Hall, Sneden's Landing, New York
        - Photographs of exterior, 1949-1963 (Box 40, Folder 760-765)
          Includes photographs of renovation with annotations about Cheer Hall, small hand-drawn floor plan as well as photographs of Susan Lowndes and East Hampton
        - Photographs of exterior, 1949-1963 (Box 41, Folder 766-776)
          Includes photographs of Murphys, renovation with annotations about Cheer Hall
        - Photographs of exterior, 1949-1963 (Box 42, Folder 777)
        - Photographs of garden at Cheer Hall and of unidentified home, 1949-1963 (Box 42, Folder 778)
        - Drawing of Cheer Hall by Lawrence Blair, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 779)
        - Negatives of photographs of Cheer Hall, undated (Box 209, Folder 1678-1680)
        - Empty negative folders for photographs of Cheer Hall, undated (Box 42, Folder 780)
      - Other Homes
        - Unidentified home, undated (Box 42, Folder 781)
        - John Dos Passos and Katy Dos Passos home, Provincetown, Massachusetts, undated (Box 42, Folder 782)
  - Photograph Albums
    - Album created by Mary Hoyt Wiborg of Wiborg family on Long Island, New York, circa 1895 (Box 43, Folder 783-784)
      Photographs accompanied by rhyming narrative describing the family's adventures
    - Album created by Mary Hoyt Wiborg containing "Photographs Taken on Fourth Trip Abroad through England, Germany, Switzerland, and Bohemia On Summer 1901 from June - September", 1901-1902 (Box 43, Folder 785)
      Includes photographs of Wiborg family with James McDonald and family, Baron and Baroness Leitenberger, Prince and Princess Hohenlohe, Graf Auersperg, Graf Lärchenfels, and Countess Dezasse.
    - Album containing photographs and clippings documenting Prince Hohenzollerns's visit to the U.S.A., 1904 (Box 43, Folder 786-787)
    - Album containing photographs from Wiborg family's trip to Europe, 1905 (Box 44, Folder 788-789)
      Includes photographs of Wiborgs in Plombières (Belgium) in countryside and learning to make "point de Venise " lace; Podiebrad and Podiebrad Castle (Bohemia) with Rumerskirch, Prince Hohenzollerns, Prince Taxis, visiting the castle, touring by boat, partridge hunting, performing, and socializing; Munich (Germany) with Mr. and Mrs. Ned Reed; Ischl and Aultaussee (Austria) at Princess Elizabeth Hohenlohe's Chalet with Princess Sara Hohenlohe, Prince Franz-Josef, Baroness Frankenstein and Baron Frankenstein Von Spiegl; on ship Kaiser Wilhelm II; Newport, Rhode Island and Clifton, Cincinnati, Ohio with photographs of Mrs. Hulbert and Mrs. Stern's lunch at "The Pillars"
    - Album containing photographs of Wiborg family in Santa Barbara, California, 1908 (Box 45, Folder 790-791)
      Includes Wiborgs photographed at "Bellosguardo" home of Mr. and Mrs. William Miller Graham, at Flower Pageant, attending parties, playing on the beach; photographs of the Atlantic Squadron anchored in the Pacific Ocean
    - Album containing photographs from Wiborg family's travels by automobile in France, 1909 May (Box 46, Folder 792)
      Includes photographs of Wiborg family and Sara Sherman traveling through northern France. Sites visited include: Fontainbleau, Millet's House (Barbizon); Château de Rambouillet (Rambouillet); Saint Germain; Château Gaillard (Les Andelys); Church at Bon-Secours, Cathédrale Notre-Dame de Rouen, Hôtel de Ville, Église St-Maclou (Rouen); Château de Bonneville (Bonneville); Villedieu-les-Poêles; La Merveille (Mont St. Michel); Château d'Angers (Angers); Azay-le-Rideau; Château de Langeais, Château de Chinon, Château d'Amboise (Indre-et-Loire); Château de Chaumont (Chaumont-sur-Loire); Blois; and attending the Grand Prix (Paris)
    - Album containing photographs of Wiborg family in East Hampton, New York, 1909 Summer (Box 47, Folder 793-794)
      Includes photographs of Sara and Gerald at the Dunes as well as Wiborg family with friends on the beach, at various social functions, and attending wedding (possibly wedding of Sara Sherman and Ledyard Mitchell)
    - Album containing photographs of Wiborg family in East Hampton, New York, circa 1905-1910 (Box 48, Folder 795-796)
      Includes three photographs of Podiebrad (Bohemia); photographs of Wiborg family and friends (including Gerald Murphy) at the Dunes, on the beach, playing tennis, riding horses, in costumes, picnicking, and horse racing; photographs of interior and exterior of Dunes
      Names of friends listed on a sheet inside album include: Monroe Robinson, Breeses (possibly William Lawrence Breese), Gerard Lambert, Rachel Lambert, Mrs. Burden?, Anita Peabody, Roger Poore, possibly Nina Floyd Crosby Eustis (later de Polignac), Betty Breese, Pauline Morton (Mrs. Dwight Davis), Cecilia May, Henry May, Gladys Vanderbilt Széchenyi (at "The Breakers," Newport, Rhode Island), Gladys Ingalls, Carolyn Postlethwaite
    - Album containing photographs of Wiborg family in Italy, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 797)
      Includes photographs of Wiborgs visiting various sites in Tuscany (such as Florence and a monastery)
    - Album containing photographs of Wiborg family in Italy, England, Ireland, and Scotland, 1913 (Box 50, Folder 798-799)